(Leonard:)- No.
- You're making her uncomfortable.
Did...? Oh, I'm sorry.
(Sheldon:)Well, if it helps you feel any better,
you're doing very well so far.
(Sheldon:)Next question. Are you fertile?
(Penny:)- What?
- I'm trying to determine...
...whether crying infants are a possibility.
- I have no immediate plans.
- If that changes, let me know.
(Sheldon:)- And finally, area rugs, pro or con?
- Pro?
(Penny:)- Alicia?
- Yes?
(Sheldon:)Welcome to the building.
(Alicia:)Thanks so much for helping me, Leonard.
LEONARD: Thank you so much for
giving me the opportunity to help.
(Penny(exiting apartment):)Oh, hey, guys.
- Penny, this is Alicia, our new neighbor.
- Hi.
(Sheldon:)Hi.
(Leonard:)I'm helping.
(Penny:)I can see.
(Sheldon:)Alicia's non-musical,
childless and pro-rug.